[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company built the Zero, the top Japanese fighter in World War Two?", "correct_answer": "Mitsubishi", "incorrect_answers": ["Nissan", "Tachikowa", "Nakajima"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national motto of what country is A Mari Usque Ad Mare, meaning From Sea to Sea in Latin?", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamaica", "Spain", "Haiti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What word denotes the ability of the muscle to transmit impulses?", "correct_answer": "Conductivity", "incorrect_answers": ["Irritability", "Extensibility", "Elasticity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many different vocalization sounds does a cat make?", "correct_answer": "100", "incorrect_answers": ["200", "50", "150"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I am a primate endemic to Madagascar. I have large, reflective eyes. I have a long tail. I have long toes, and opposable thumbs, useful for grasping tree branches. What am I?", "correct_answer": "A lemur", "incorrect_answers": ["An iguana", "An ape", "A monkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was arrested and imprisoned in 1849 for engaging in revolutionary activity against the ruler, but became one of his countrys greatest writers.", "correct_answer": "Dostoevsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Hugo", "Engels", "Cervantes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Nice Dreams, Chong is mistaken for what rock legend by a woman in a Chinese restaurant?", "correct_answer": "Jerry Garcia", "incorrect_answers": ["Santana", "Neil Young", "David Crosby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the symbol for Cobalt?", "correct_answer": "Co", "incorrect_answers": ["Ct", "C", "Cb"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This coenzyme is naturally produced by a specific algae.  It is used for transforming food into energy that the body will use to perform all its activities.  It is also a powerful antioxidant.", "correct_answer": "Q 10", "incorrect_answers": ["Riboflavin", "Thiamin", "Niacin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "By amending its Opium Act in 1976, the government of which country decided to treat possession of up to 30 grams of marijuana as an activity not for prosecution, detection or arrest?", "correct_answer": "Holland", "incorrect_answers": ["Columbia", "Canada", "USA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Layer ingredients in a shot glass in the following order: 15 ml Creme De Cacao white liqueur, 15 ml  Blue curacao liqueur, 15 ml Scotch Whisky.", "correct_answer": "African Violet", "incorrect_answers": ["Kiss Me Quick", "Martini Perfect", "Mexican Coffee"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rotterdam, located in the province of South Holland, is a major Dutch port.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]